Now is the moment you've all been waiting for. The results are in, and it's time to meet your top 10!
All right, prepare yourselves, folks!
In 10th place, 75th generation trainee, Memori Kishida!
I'm Memori Kishida!
First of all, I'd like to say thank you from the bottom of my heart. I can't believe I'm standing here after dreaming of being a successor for so long. I would be lying if I said it hasn't been a frustrating journey, but through every tear and hardship, my friends were always by my side!
Memori...
I'm sorry. I'm not very good at expressing my emotions, so I just bottled them up and never showed them. However, because I had friends who always got even more frustrated, who cried and got angry alongside me, because of them, I've been able to keep trying without giving up!
That's not true at all. You saved me by always smiling for me, and by always being there. You supported me every step of the way. That's why I've made it this far.
Even though I'm not a successor to have been chosen in the general elections, this is truly my happiest moment!
But I still have the promise I made to my friends! Kanata! The general elections are just the beginning of our journey! Let's both become successors as soon as we can, okay?
It's like Memori's looking down on us.
This is... kind of embarrassing.
Yuka?
To be painfully honest, I had given up on being elected the moment the election was announced. But she... kept working.
I wouldn't be so sure of that! The general elections give everyone an equal opportunity to shine, no matter who they are!
I didn't realize how right she was!
Mm-hmm.
She gives me hope! Let's do our best!
Memori-san is amazing!
Then... what about Chiyuri?
If I'm chosen in the general elections...
You'll quit Zero-Zero?
Yes, ma'am. If I remain a part of Zero-Zero, I'll only cause trouble for the others.
I don't get it. If that's the case, why didn't you say you would quit sooner?
What?
You were ninth place. True, it was just the preliminaries, but each of those votes came from fans who adore you. What you're planning on doing would be spitting on those feelings.
Those votes didn't come from my strength. It was because of Zodiac. They're all being fooled. The only reason I was chosen is because of my father's power.
If you're elected, you'll have to make a speech on stage.
Oh!
We leave it up to members to decide what they want to say. It's not my place to tell you what to do. But if you intend to quit, tell them yourself when you're up on that stage.
If I'm elected, I have to tell them. I have to do it here.
Moving on, the ninth place announcement.
Your choice for ninth place is...
Tenth generation, Sei Miyazawa!
Oh, wow!
Sei!
I'm so honored! Everyone, thank you for your support!
Sei Miyazawa!
All right!
Hey, Megumi, sit down.
Huh?
Oh, oops.
Megumi-san seems happy.
Mm-hmm.
I voted for Sonata ten times when the ballots were open.
You what?!
You should've voted for yourself like I did, Suzu!
We shouldn't vote at all! The whole point of this thing is to let the fans choose!
And voting for yourself?!
Leave it to Sonata to get Yuka riled!
Ugh!
Come on, now!
Ah! Yuka could appear during the broadcast at any moment, you piece of junk!
Ugh! I bet this is the D.E.S. is doing!
That's right. It couldn't possibly be that you never take care of that thing!
Oh!
Come on, Dad! You can fix anything!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Oh, sure! Just leave it to me!
I'm sorry about this, Motomiya-san. You came all the way here to see the broadcast.
It's all right. I just hope that I'm not bothering you by coming here and loitering.
My husband will be at work for a while longer, and I felt so nervous watching it at home by myself.
I understand. Well, we're probably not missing much. They're so new, it might be tough for them to be elected.
I know. It's just... my daughter's not very good with competitions.
Everyone seems so unhappy. I don't like this. It's scary.
In 8th place is... 11th generation, Tomomi Itano!
Tomo-chi-pa's already being announced!
But she was third in the preliminary announcement!
That's not the chance!
She was third again!
Tomo-chi-pa's already being announced!
I'm Tomo-mi. Thank you very much.
This is my first time to be participating in the general elections.
My older sister, the 10th Tomo-mi, stood in this very spot in the last election.
It's tradition that all daughters of the Itano household must audition for AKB-0048.
In order to learn, I sat in the audience just like you and watched.
My sister was 8th place.
Just like me, she had fallen a considerable number of ranks from the initial results.
My sister overcame her tears and smiled during her speech.
But as I look around me, I could see her fans sobbing and heartbroken.
It was as though they were crying in her place.
For the first time in my life, I felt jealous of my sister.
I wished to join Zero Zero and be loved by everyone just like her.
Not just for my family, but for myself.
Looking out at the audience, I can see people crying for me,
just like they did for my sister that day.
Next time, I'd like to see you cry tears of joy instead of tears of frustration.
I'll work harder than ever before and be worthy of tears.
I am honored to achieve the same rake as my sister.
Thank you for staying with me this far.
I never thought I'd see her cry like that.
I know, right?
I'm a really big fan and I've decided to support you.
I'll make sure you're elected.
I'll do my best for the general elections, too.
I never realized.
Our fans put their hopes and love into us.
I'm jealous.
Huh?
If you get to stand on that stage, you have an opportunity to answer the fans' love and return it to them.
Yeah.
Someday I want to thank them.
And I'll do it from up on that stage.
They're right.
We're not alone.
We can work with the people who love us and return that love in kind.
That's what the general elections are about.
Yeah.
In seventh place, eighth generation, Haruna Kojima.
Thank you very much for voting for me.
You're the reason I'm standing here tonight.
It's been a while since my last general elections.
So I was hoping we could have fun together.
And we have.
I was shocked to find out I was fifth place in the preliminary results.
But really, but receiving seventh place today feels just right.
And I can't thank you enough for everything.
I'm so frustrated!
Koji Haru-san!
A place where the always cheerful Koji Haru-san can cry her heart out.
A place where she can admit she's frustrated.
The general elections are amazing!
Because of my father's power, I gained more fans.
But I couldn't accept it.
Those votes didn't come from my strength.
It was because of Zodiac.
And I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was because of Zodiac.
They're all being fooled!
Not my strength.
Just my father's power.
What am I saying?
All the people who voted for me,
no matter how they reached that decision,
they all like me.
They're all people who love me.
Moving on.
The sixth place announcement.
Uh...
Chiyari?
What's wrong?
I'm in...
In such an amazing place.
In such a wonderful place.
I can't do it.
I don't want to graduate.
What are you talking about?
Graduate?
In sixth place is 77th generation trainee, Chiyari Zodo!
Yes.
What are you looking up there?
Chiarijan, are you all right?
Chiarijan's acting weird.
Don't worry, it's pretty calming.
It can be overwhelming.
Many members have hyperventilated before.
She'll be fine.
I hope you're right.
Chiarijan's the last person I expected to lose it so badly.
Chiarijan, are you able to stand by on your own?
Okay, give it your best.
I have this 77th generation.
Trainee, Chiarijan's the last person I have to say it.
I have to tell them.
All right, Chiarijan, it's time to show us your decision.
Chiarijan, what?
What?
I... I... I am... I'm going to...
I... I just want to say...
I... I... I love each and every one of you!
Chiarijan...
I love you.
I wouldn't be here without you.
Without my friends and my fans, I'd still be lost.
I want to continue to be a member of AKB-0048 with all of the people that I love.
We love you too!
I can't believe she said that!
Amazing!
I could never be that direct.
This is nothing like the AKB trials were.
What's wrong with her?
She's acting all weird.
Maybe.
But I really understand how she feels.
I'll continue to work hard.
Thank you very much!
Chiarijan...
Chiarijan's so brilliant.
And so far away.
I guess Chiarijan can be cute when the conditions are right.
I hope she's sure of herself.
In fifth place is Mark III, Mayu Watanabe!
Thank you for your support.
I look forward to many years with you all.
In fourth place, sixth generation,
Yuki Kashiwagi!
I'm aiming for the top and I won't stop till I'm there.
I'll make you fall in love with me.
I don't know about you,
but I'm pretty sure there's no chance
our names aren't getting called this time around.
Maybe, but I still think it's amazing
that two trainees were selected.
Yeah, it really is amazing,
but I don't know.
Something's not right.
My legs feel cold.
Maybe the air conditioning's too strong.
In third place is 10th generation,
Sayaka Akimono!
Thank you so much, everyone!
Thank you, thank you!
I can't say it enough!
What is this?
I can't hear anyone.
I can't see Chiari very well, either.
Now then,
there are only two seats remaining.
Who will our top two members be?
Here we go.
Hold on to your seats, folks.
With 1,184,848 points,
your second place winner is...
5th generation Minami Takahashi!
Step right up, Takemina!
I'm 5th generation Minami Takahashi.
Thank you all for your support.
The general elections answered a question,
one I've had in my heart for a while now.
Those who succeed Minami Takahashi
have been captains of Zero Zero,
and I've done my very best
to support my members as their captain.
But I may have been wrong.
Perhaps, in the end,
I was the one who actually was being supported.
Today, I compete against rivals and friends.
Takemina-san!
Because of the friendships I've made here,
I have been able to work hard until today.
All the juniors who have yet to bloom,
all the rivals blooming with me
who never forget to give it their all
every minute of every day,
and finally,
all the fans who have watched over us from the start.
All of these have supported me.
And I can't begin to thank you enough for that.
Please continue to support AKB-0048.
So cool.
Takahita-san,
I'll always be your biggest fan in the universe.
Big Fist, you're leaking all over the place.
It's finally time to announce
the first place member of the general elections.
The year 0048 general elections first place winner
is none other than...
Knight's generation Yuko Oshima!
I want you!
Yuko-san!
Yuko-chan!
Yuko-chan, congrats. You've earned it.
Thank you very much, Toko-san.
I want you to say something to your fans.
Yuko-chan, congrats. You've earned it.
Thank you very much, Toko-san.
Yuko-san!
Yuko-chan, congrats. You've earned it.
Thank you very much, Toko-san.
Step up and say something to your fans.
I'm 9th generation Oshima Yuko.
First place.
My rank makes me feel so...
so clearly how much you all love me.
I have never been this happy in my life.
I... I wish I could bask in this happiness forever.
But what I'm really after lies beyond this happiness
and has always been the ultimate goal I've strived for.
It continues to drive me each day.
My greatest rival is still Achan,
the 13th generation Maeda Atsuko.
Yuko.
Becoming first place
and the center of our next single isn't good enough.
I will continue working as the center
and shine even brighter than I do at this moment
so I can be the one and only Center Nova.
I will become a Center Nova
who shines even brighter than Achan did.
I swear I will.
And even if I become the Center Nova,
I will not disappear.
All I ask is that you follow me,
and I will show you, Mr. Nova,
the greatest brilliance that a center star
can shine upon the sky.
Yuko-san's so cool.
I can't contain myself.
Magisa?
You all right there?
She's really done it this time, hasn't she?
Tsubasa.
Achan.
Please,
protect those girls from me.
The members standing by will now leave the venue.
Let's send them off with a round of applause.
Someday, I want to stand up there.
No.
Someday, I will stand there.
CENTRE NOVA.
CHUN.
Thank you.
I was scared of it.
I was afraid that by being compared to my friends and by being forced to compete with all of them, that I would change.
But I didn't dislike the members who competed against each other at all.
Neither did they.
They were so cool.
So were you, Chiri.
You shined so brightly.
It was absolutely amazing.
Nagisa.
But you know, that's why we can't end things here.
We're just getting started.
So, Chiri.
Watch out!
I'm a powerful opponent.
Nagisa.
Achon?
This attack concert will be performed by the elected members.
Let's go nuts!
I have nothing to lose!
Don't give up!
Our plan isn't over yet!
This is the planet's secret?